Alaska
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Alaska, 2.1.3.2
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - native peoples, circa 1915 - 1916; 15 (Box 1515)
    - [Animal skins hanging in a camp in Alaska], 3
    - [Three native Alaskans], 4
    - [Native family and their tent in Alaska], 5
    - [Native Alaskan and two kayaks], 6
    - [Two native Alaskans in their kayaks], 7
    - [Two native alaskan women and one child], 8
    - [Alaskan natives looking at boats], 9
    - [Native tents in Alaska], 10
    - [Native Alaskan working on animal skin], 11
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Nome, Alaska, circa 1915 - 1916; 16 (Box 1515)
    - [Shops in Alaska], 1
    - [Boats on the waterfront in Alaska], 2
    - [Men in Alaska working], 3
    - [People boarding boat in Alaska], 4
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Pacific Northwest, circa 1915 - 1916; 17 (Box 1515)
    - "All agreed, as the steamer 'Alameda' sailed through the straits of Juan de Fuca, leaving Puget Sound, that the trip ahead of us was a perilous one." Picture by L. J. Thomas, 1
    - Verso: "All agreed, as the steamer 'Alameda' sailed through the straits of Juan de Fuca, leaving Puget Sound, that the trip ahead of us was a perilous one." Picture by L. J. Thomas, 1-verso
    - Fishing boats near Prince Rupert. Inside passage, 2
    - Verso: Fishing boats near Prince Rupert. Inside passage, 2-verso
    - [Young girl standing outside a long cabin "Tolovana"], 3
    - [Person sleeping in bed in Alaska], 4
    - ["Royal Alexandra"building in Alaska], 5
    - [Alaskan farmers in the field], 6
    - [Alaskan man and his garden], 7
    - [Man in front of wooden house in Alaska], 8
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Pacific Northwest (Mount Rainier National Park), circa 1915 - 1916; 18 (Box 1515)
    - [Cars and train, "Chicago Milwauke", in Alaska], 1
    - [Alaskan evergreens], 2
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Pacific Northwest (Olympic peninsula), circa 1915 - 1916; 19 (Box 1515)
    - [River in Alaska], 1
    - [Dead trees in Alaska], 2
    - [Car on Alaskan forest road], 3
    - [Car driving in Alaska], 4
    - [Ten people in a boat in Alaska], 5
    - [Waterfront homes in Alaska], 6
    - [Man in Alaska], 7
    - [Bridge in Alaska], 8
    - [Man and tree in Alaska], 9
    - [Boat in Alaskan waters], 10
    - [Man on boat in Alaska], 11
    - [Man on boat in Alaska], 12
    - [Boats on Alaskan waters], 13
    - [Farm in Alaska], 14
    - [Waterfront town in Alaska], 15
    - [Small town in Alaska], 16
  Box 1516
- Alaska, 2.1.3.2
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Pacific Northwest (shipyard), circa 1915 - 1916; 1 (Box 1516)
    - [Shipyard in Alaska], 1
    - [Boat and storehouse in Alaskan shipyard], 2
    - [Shipyard in Alaska], 3
    - [Two boats in Alaska], 4
    - [Men working at Alaskan shipyard], 5
    - [Men working at Alaskan shipyard], 6
    - [Boat on Alaskan waters], 7
    - [Livestock on boat in Alaska], 8
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Peel River and Porcupine Indians, circa 1915 - 1916; 2 (Box 1516)
    - Former chief of the Porcupines making snowshoes. This Indian resigned as chief of the tribe in 1888, ten years before gold was discovered in the Klondike, on account of old age. This picture was taken July 2nd, 1916, 1
    - Verso: Former chief of the Porcupines making snowshoes. This Indian resigned as chief of the tribe in 1888, ten years before gold was discovered in the Klondike, on account of old age. This picture was taken July 2nd, 1916, 1-verso
    - Peel and Porcupine Indian children and squaws, 2
    - Verso: Peel and Porcupine Indian children and squaws, 2-verso
    - [Peel and Porcupine Indian childrean and squaws], 3
    - [Peel and Porcupine Indian children and squaws], 4
    - [Four Indian men in Alaska], 5
    - [Indian men in Alaska], 6
    - [Alaskan Indian men], 7
    - [Indian men playing ball in Alaska], 8
    - [Indian families in Alaska], 9
    - [Peel and Porcupine Indians surrounding camera], 10
    - [Peel and Porcupine Indian men], 11
    - [Group of Peel and Porcupine Indians in Alaska], 12
    - [Tents in Alaska], 13
    - [Peel and Porcupine Indinas in their tents], 14
    - [Two men among tents in Alaska], 15
    - [Group of people in tents in Alaska], 16
    - [Peel and Porcupine Indians], 17
    - [Dogs and Alaskan Indians], 18
    - [Peel and Porcupine Indian families], 19
    - [Peel and Porcupine children], 20
    - [Alaskan Indians with dead goose], 21
    - [Alaskan Indian under makeshift tee-pee], 22
    - [Peel and Porcupine Indian camp], 23
    - [Alaskan woman and her child], 24
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Ruby, Alaska, circa 1915 - 1916; 3 (Box 1516)
    - ["The Record Citizen" shop in Alaska], 1
    - [Waterfront neighborhood in Alaska], 2
    - [Houses on Alaskan waterfront], 3
    - [Houses on an Alaskan shore], 4
    - [Wooden building on Alaskan waterfront], 5
    - [Dogs pulling a cart in Alaska], 6
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - ships along the coast, circa 1915 - 1916; 4 (Box 1516)
    - [Ship off an Alaskan coast], 1
    - [Ship off an Alaskan coast], 2
    - [Ship in Alaskan waters], 3
    - [Alaskan ship], 4
    - [Alaskan ship off the coast], 5
    - [Men on ship in Alaska], 6
    - [Ship in Alaska], 7
    - [Ship in Alaska], 8
    - [Upper deck on ship in Alaska], 9
    - [Ships off the coast in Alaska], 10
    - [Ships by the coast in Alaska], 11
    - [Ships by the coast in Alaska], 12
    - [Ship in Alaska], 13
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Skagway/Haines/Atlin/Whitehorse, Alaska, circa 1915 - 1916; 5 (Box 1516)
    - The Midnight sun taken at Fort Yukon Alaska June 21st 1916 at 12 o'clock midnight, 1
    - Verso: The Midnight sun taken at Fort Yukon Alaska June 21st 1916 at 12 o'clock midnight, 1-verso
    - View of the midnight sun Fort Yukon Alaska. Taken from the deck of the Str. [steamer] "Casea" June 21st [19]16. Str. [steamer ] "Whitehorse" in the distance, 2
    - Verso: View of the midnight sun Fort Yukon Alaska. Taken from the deck of the Str. [steamer] "Casea" June 21st [19]16. Str. [steamer ] "Whitehorse" in the distance, 2-verso
    - [Forest road in Alaska], 3
    - [Mountain range in Alaska], 4
    - [River in Alaska], 5
    - [Alaskan family], 6
    - [Alaskan family], 7
    - [Group of women in Alaska], 8
    - [Group of women in Alaska], 9
    - [People sledding in Alaska], 10
    - [People sledding in Alaska], 11
    - [Farmhouse in Alaska], 12
    - [Alaska mountain range], 13
    - [Mountain range in Alaska], 14
    - [Mountains in Alaska], 15
    - [People on train in Alaska], 16
    - [Men standing in train car in Alaska], 17
    - [Men standing in train car in Alaska], 18
    - [Men standing in train car in Alaska], 19
    - [Men standing in train car in Alaska], 20
    - [Alaska landscape], 21
    - [Man in train engine, "Duchess", in Alaska], 22
    - ["AB No. 19" building in Alaska], 23
    - [People on bridge leading to train in Alaska], 24
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Tanana, Alaska, circa 1915 - 1916; 6 (Box 1516)
    - Hairdressing parlor and manicure establishment, at Nenana, a town in the interior where the present headquarters of the Tanana Valley railroad construction camp is located. By L. J. Thomas, 1
    - Verso: Hairdressing parlor and manicure establishment, at Nenana, a town in the interior where the present headquarters of the Tanana Valley railroad construction camp is located. By L. J. Thomas, 1-verso
    - [Tower House inn (?) in Alaska], 2
    - ["Scott Kay and Mickey Woods Headquarters" building in Alaska], 3
    - [Small town in Alaska], 4
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Lowell Thomas, undated; 7 (Box 1516)
    - [Lowell Thomas pointing in Alaska], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas pointing in Alaska], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas pointing in Alaska], 3
    - [London-Trafalgar Square] Postcard, 4
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) on ship in Alaska], 5
    - [Busy city street in Alaska (?)], 6
    - [Busy city street (backwards)], 7
    - [Train, "Duchess"], 8
    - [Group of men in fishing boat in Alaska], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) & a group of men cooking over a fire in Alaska], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) & others sitting outside a log cabin in Alaska], 11
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Lowell Thomas automobile trip, circa 1915 - 1916; 8 (Box 1516)
    - Autoing [sic] in the wilds of Alaska, 1
    - Verso: Autoing [sic] in the wilds of Alaska, 1-verso
    - Bishop P.T. Rowe and Mr. Thomas on a 400 mile auto trip through the heart of the Alaskan wilderness. Alaska needs millions of dollars for roads to help develop its resources, 2
    - Verso: Bishop P.T. Rowe and Mr. Thomas on a 400 mile auto trip through the heart of the Alaskan wilderness. Alaska needs millions of dollars for roads to help develop its resources, 2-verso
    - Motoring through the heart of Alaska with the temperature 90 above zero, 3
    - Verso: Motoring through the heart of Alaska with the temperature 90 above zero, 3-verso
    - The government has built an automobile road 470 miles long through the heart of Alaska from Valdez to Fairbanks. A machine has to be overhauled and sometimes completely replaced after about 2 trips, 4
    - Verso: The government has built an automobile road 470 miles long through the heart of Alaska from Valdez to Fairbanks. A machine has to be overhauled and sometimes completely replaced after about 2 trips, 4-verso
    - Building a government road in Alaska. By L.J. Thomas, 5
    - Verso: Building a government road in Alaska. By L.J. Thomas, 5-verso
    - Motoring in the Interior, 6
    - Verso: Motoring in the Interior, 6-verso
    - [no description], 7
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Lowell Thomas in fur coat, circa 1915 - 1916; 9 (Box 1516)
    - Lowell Thomas in fur coat, 1
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Lowell Thomas with motion picture camera, circa 1915 - 1916; 10 (Box 1516)
    - Prof. Thomas and his moving picture camera at the head of Miles Canyon just before he and Ed Dixon, Yukon Councilor from White Horse, shot the famous rapids, 1
    - Verso: Prof. Thomas and his moving picture camera at the head of Miles Canyon just before he and Ed Dixon, Yukon Councilor from White Horse, shot the famous rapids, 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas on the Miles Canyon (?) with his moving picture camera], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas on the Miles Canyon (?) with his moving picture camera], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas on the Miles Canyon (?) with his moving picture camera], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas & his moving picture camera on a small boat], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas & his moving picture camera on a small boat], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas & his moving picture camera on a small boat], 7
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Lowell Thomas at the petrified forest, circa 1915 - 1916; 11 (Box 1516)
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others sitting on a fence near the petrified forest], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others sitting on a fence near the petrified forest], 2
    - [Building atop a cliff], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at the petrified forest], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in front of cliffs], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in a cage at the petrified forest], 6
    - [Petrified tree(?) at the petrified forest], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas standing on a fallen tree at the petrified forest], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas looking at a cut up tree trunk at the petrified forest], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) examining tree trunk at the petrified forest], 10
    - [The petrified forest (?)], 11
    - [Cut up tree trunks at the petrified forest (?)], 12
    - [Rocky landscape at the petrified forest (?)], 13
    - [Rocky landscape scene at the petrified forest (?)], 14
    - [At the bottom of a cliff at the petrified forest (?)], 15
    - [Cliffs at the petrified forest (?)], 16
    - [Lake and cliff landscape at the petrified forest (?)], 17
    - [Cliffs & plateaus at the petrified forest (?)], 18
    - [Men standing in barren landscape at the petrified forest (?)], 19
    - [Man on the edge of a barren landscape at the petrified forest (?)], 20
    - [Man examining tree trunks at the petrified forest (?)], 21
    - [Cut up tree trunks at the petrified forest (?)], 22
    - [Tree trunks at the petrified forest (?)], 23
    - [Building in the middle of the petrified forest (?)], 24
    - Two large tree trunks in the petrified forest (?)], 25
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - trip over the Valdez Trail, circa 1915 - 1916; 12 (Box 1516)
    - Gov't road building in Alaska, 1
    - Verso: Gov't road building in Alaska, 1-verso
    - [Three men standing in front of a car in Alaska], 2
    - [Two men driving a car in Alaska], 3
    - [Three men standing around a car in Alaska], 4
    - [Men fixing a car in Alaska], 5
    - [Men walking along a mountain road in Alaska], 6
    - [Tents in Alaska], 7
    - [Car on a dirt road in Alaska], 8
    - [Four men in Alaska], 9
    - [Car going over a log bridge in Alaska ], 10
    - [Car on a waterfront bridge in Alaska], 11
    - [Car and horse in the middle of an Alaskan field], 12
    - [Log cabins in Alaska], 13
    - [Man and dog outside of a log cabin in Alaska], 14
    - [Bunk beds in Alaska], 15
    - [River and mountains in Alaska], 16
    - [Mountain range in Alaska], 17
    - [Hills in Alaska], 18
    - [Alaska landscape], 19
    - [Alaskan landscape], 20
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Vassar girls, circa 1915 - 1916; 13 (Box 1516)
    - Vassar girls panning gold on the Nome beach, August 12, 1916, 1
    - Verso: Vassar girls panning gold on the Nome beach, August 12, 1916, 1-verso
    - [Vassar girls panning gold on the Nome beach in Alaska], 2
    - [Vassar girls panning gold on the Nome beach in Alaska], 3
    - [Mrs. Napolean standing on boat deck in Alaska], 4
    - [Mrs. Napolean leaning on row boat in Alaska], 5
    - [Mrs. Napolean leaning on row boat in Alaska], 6
    - Mrs. Napoleon crossing the Hellespoint., 7
    - Verso: Mrs. Napoleon crossing the Hellespoint., 7-verso
    - [Mrs. Napolean on the Umatilla N.Y. in Alaska], 8
    - [Two women standing on boat in Alaska], 9
    - [Mrs. Napolean and another standing on a dock in Alaska], 10
    - [Mrs. Napolean and another standing on a dock in Alaska], 11
    - [Mrs. Napolean and another standing on a dock in Alaska], 12
    - [Mrs. Napolean sitting on rocks in Alaska], 13
    - [Mrs. Napolean sitting on rocks in Alaska], 14
    - [Mrs. Napolean standing on rocks in Alaska], 15
    - [Mrs. Napolean standing on rocks in Alaska], 16
    - [Mrs. Napolean standing on rocks in Alaska], 17
    - [Mrs. Napolean pointing at something in Alaska], 18
    - [Mrs. Napolean and a gentleman in Alaska], 19
    - [Group of people in Alaska], 20
    - [Three women on the shore in Alaska], 21
    - [Woman standing by bushes in Alaska], 22
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - Vassar girls with Lowell Thomas, circa 1915 - 1916; 14 (Box 1516)
    - Vassar girls with Lowell Thomas, 1
  - Alaska: Leather trunk series - vistas, circa 1915 - 1916; 15 (Box 1516)
    - [Snowy mountains in Alaska], 1
    - [Mountains in Alaska], 2
    - [Alaskan mountain and water scene], 3
    - [Snowy Alaskan mountains off in the distance], 4
    - [Snowy mountains in Alaska], 5
    - [Small lake in a forest in Alaska], 6
    - [Mountains in Alaska], 7
  - Alaska: Minnie Marry and Miki Paneak [color photograph], 1971 July; 16 (Box 1516)
    - To Lowell Thomas, Sr. From Dianne Gudgel, Anchorage, AK; Minnie Marry and Miki Paneak, Anaktuvuk Pass, AK, July '71, 1
    - Verso: To Lowell Thomas, Sr. From Dianne Gudgel, Anchorage, AK; Minnie Marry and Miki Paneak, Anaktuvuk Pass, AK, July '71, 1-verso
  - Alaska: Mount Bertha, 1940; 17 (Box 1516)
    - Mount Bertha; Alaska 1940, 1
    - Verso: Mount Bertha; Alaska 1940, 1-verso
  - Alaska: Lowell Thomas in bear suit with Husky dog by his side, circa 1915 - 1916; 18 (Box 1516)
    - Prof. Lowell Jackson Thomas, of Princeton University, with his huskey [sic], "Fang", 1
    - Verso: Prof. Lowell Jackson Thomas, of Princeton University, with his huskey [sic], "Fang", 1-verso
    - Prof. Lowell Jackson Thomas, of Princeton University, Alaskan Explorer, Geologist and Lecturer, 2
    - Verso: Prof. Lowell Jackson Thomas, of Princeton University, Alaskan Explorer, Geologist and Lecturer, 2-verso
    - Prof. Lowell J. Thomas, of Princeton, 3
    - Verso: Prof. Lowell J. Thomas, of Princeton, 3-verso
    - Arctic 1914, 4
    - Verso: Arctic 1914, 4-verso
    - Lowell Thomas as he appeared when he lead [sic] two expeditions into the Arctic at the age of twenty, 5
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas as he appeared when he lead [sic] two expeditions into the Arctic at the age of twenty, 5-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas in bear suit with his huskey], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas in bear suit with his huskey], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas in bear suit with his huskey], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas in bear suit with his huskey], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas in bear suit with his huskey], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas in bear suit with his huskey], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas in bear suit with his huskey], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas in bear suit with his huskey], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas in bear suit with his huskey], 14
  - Lowell Thomas in bear suit with Husky dog by his side, circa 1915 - 1916; 19 (Box 1516)
    - Caption: Alaska; Lowell Jackson Thomas, "Greatest Alaskan Traveloguer", 1
  - Lowell Thomas in bear suit with Husky dog by his side, circa 1915 - 1916; 20 (Box 1516)
    - 'Prof. Lowell J. Thomas, of Princeton' and 'Prof. Lowell Jackson Thomas, of Princeton University, Alaskan Explorer, Geologist and Lecturer' [46 copies], 1
    - Verso: 'Prof. Lowell J. Thomas, of Princeton' and 'Prof. Lowell Jackson Thomas, of Princeton University, Alaskan Explorer, Geologist and Lecturer', 1-verso
  Box 1517
- Alaska, 2.1.3.2
  - Alaska: Lowell Thomas, Jr., 1964; 1 (Box 1517)
    - L.T. Jr. addressing G.O.P. National Convention in San Francisco, 1964, 1
    - Verso: L.T. Jr. addressing G.O.P. National Convention in San Francisco, 1964, 1-verso
    - [L.T. Jr. addressing G.O.P National Convention in San Francisco, 1964], 2
    - [L.T. Jr. at the G.O.P National Convention in San Franciso, 1964], 3
    - Russian Orthodox Xmas, Akutan, Alaska, 4
    - Verso: Russian Orthodox Xmas, Akutan, Alaska; Mac's Foto, 10544, 315-4th Ave., Anchorage, Alaska, 4-verso
    - [Two men going into a "Merry Christmas" building], 5
    - Verso: Mac's Foto, 10542, 315-4th Ave., Anchorage, Alaska, 5-verso
    - [L.T. Jr. receiving "The Alaska Press Club" member certificate], 6
    - Verso: Ward W. Wells, Photographer; 327 Fifth Avenue, Anchorage, Alaska; Neg. No. 5052-2, 6-verso
    - [L.T. Jr. holding a large crab], 7
    - Verso: Mac's Foto, 11176, 315-4th Ave., Anchorage, Alaska, 7-verso
    - [L.T. Jr, holding a large crab], 8
    - [L.T. Jr. holding a large crab], 9
    - [Three people and an airplane in Alaska], 10
    - [Three people and an airplane in Alaska], 11
    - [Three people and an airplane in Alaska (negative format)], 12
  - Alaska: Lowell Thomas, Jr. [color photographs], circa 1979; 2 (Box 1517)
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. with unidentified man], 1
    - [Man in front of an airplane in Alaska], 2
    - [Two men and an airplane in Alaska], 3
    - [unidentified individuals], 4
  - Alaska: Lowell Thomas, Jr., 1963; 3 (Box 1517)
    - Surprise Glacier - Sept. 15, '63 - 5,400' altitude; L.T. and David Crews - Spring snow!, 1
    - Verso: Surprise Glacier - Sept. 15, '63 - 5,400' altitude; L.T. and David Crews - Spring snow!, 1-verso
  - Alaska: Lowell Thomas, Jr., undated; 4 (Box 1517)
    - Note: Long after World War II, L.T., Jr. and his flying pal, Ed Seiler, found the first world flight Douglas amphibian on the mountain in Alaska where it crashed in 1924, 1
    - [L.T. Jr. at the site of the Douglas amphibian crash, Alaska], 2
    - [L.T. Jr. at the site where the Douglas amphibian crashed in Alaska], 3
    - [L.T. "flying" the Douglas amphibian in Alaska], 4
    - [L.T. "flying" the Douglas amphibian in Alaska], 5
    - [L.T. Jr. (?) skiing in Alaska?], 6
    - [White kangaroo mother with two babies, Alaska], 7
  - Alaska: Vance photographs, 1929 - 1930; 5 (Box 1517)
    - V-1; William Vance dressed in Eskimo costume. Photo taken at Eskimo Point, 1
    - Verso: V-1; William Vance dressed in Eskimo costume. Photo taken at Eskimo Point, 1-verso
    - V-2; William Vance dressed in Eskimo costume. Photo taken at Eskimo Point, 2
    - Verso: V-2; William Vance dressed in Eskimo costume. Photo taken at Eskimo Point, 2-verso
    - V-3; Hudsons Bay Company Post at Tevane. Note the way the snow drifts over the house, 3
    - Verso: V-3; Hudsons Bay Company Post at Tevane. Note the way the snow drifts over the house, 3-verso
    - V-4; Nanya, our guide from Tevane to Eskimo Point, 4
    - Verso: V-4; Nanya, our guide from Tevane to Eskimo Point, 4-verso
    - V-5; The pontoons of this plane filled up during the night and the tail sank in so that the door was just level with the surface of the water. It is here shown after several hours' work, 5
    - Verso: V-5; The pontoons of this plane filled up during the night and the tail sank in so that the door was just level with the surface of the water. It is here shown after several hours' work, 5-verso
    - V-6; Jim Vance and Pat Reid, 6
    - Verso: V-6; Jim Vance and Pat Reid, 6-verso
    - V-7; Albert and his little girl Anana, 7
    - Verso: V-7; Albert and his little girl Anana, 7-verso
    - V-8; Vance with a beard, 8
    - Verso: V-8; Vance with a beard, 8-verso
    - V-9; Eskimo tent at Baker Lake. There is an assortment of caribou hides unsold, with guns, 9
    - Verso: V-9; Eskimo tent at Baker Lake. There is an assortment of caribou hides unsold, with guns, 9-verso
    - V-10; Taken at Churchill on the 6th of May, 1929. Left to right: Vance, Hugh Conn, General Inspector of Hudsons Bay Company, Tom Creighton one of the discoverers of the Flinn Flawn [Flin Flon] Mine, Burke[?] Schiller, and Joe Hunter, 10
    - Verso: V-10; Taken at Churchill on the 6th of May, 1929. Left to right: Vance, Hugh Conn, General Inspector of Hudsons Bay Company, Tom Creighton one of the discoverers of the Flinn Flawn [Flin Flon] Mine, Burke[?] Schiller, and Joe Hunter, 10-verso
    - V-11; An airplane on the ice at Churchill, 11
    - Verso: V-11; An airplane on the ice at Churchill, 11-verso
    - V-12; An airplane on the ice at Churchill, 12
    - Verso: V-12; An airplane on the ice at Churchill, 12-verso
    - Verso: V-13; Fish hanging on a clothes line. Fish dried in this manner would keep indefinitely. Large quantities are dried every summer both for dog food and human consumption during the winter, 13
    - V-13; Fish hanging on a clothes line. Fish dried in this manner would keep indefinitely. Large quantities are dried every summer both for dog food and human consumption during the winter, 13-verso
    - To my friends J.D. Vance + Brian Blasdale from A. Dugalle, Canadian National Photographer, 30-3-30, 14
    - Verso: V-14; Photo taken at the end of our journey at mile 327 Hudsons Bay Railway. This was taken the day after we reached this place. We had both shaved and washed several times, although there are indications that it does not look like it, 14-verso
    - V-15; Typical Eskimo woman's outfit, 15
    - Verso: V-15; Typical Eskimo woman's outfit, 15-verso
    - V-16; Rather a fine old man, a native. Note that his beard is iced up, 16
    - Verso: V-16; Rather a fine old man, a native. Note that his beard is iced up, 16-verso
    - V-17; A native with his beard frozen, 17
    - Verso: V-17; A native with his beard frozen, 17-verso
    - V-18; A young woman by the name of Attah. Very typical of Eskimo women in appearance. She is of the tribe Ivilingmuit, 18
    - Verso: V-18; A young woman by the name of Attah. Very typical of Eskimo women in appearance. She is of the tribe Ivilingmuit, 18-verso